

NGUYỄN DIỆU HƯƠNG Software Developer / Translator

/ Editor

9/4/1999

8

0961578499

duyhung2h@outlook.com

🚹 101A Phuong Mai, Ha Noi

https://aislingvt.vercel.app/resume? cv=huong

# **Skills**

HTML, CSS, SCSS



**English** 







Java, Python, JSP, Postman, Firebase, JSON, BIRT report, Angular, SOL



Vue, C#, MongoDBXML, JQuery, NodeJs



- My Language skill: C1 English (proficient), N5 Japanese
- My Language skill: C1 English

# **OBJECTIVE**

I have been designing and creating websites for over 2 years. I have experience designing and writing websites mainly in ReactJS, and have a creative mind. If you want to boost your business with a great React website, then let's talk!

I'm looking to join an inclusive company which doesn't discriminate peoples based on their race / gender / culture as a freelancer / salaryman!

My English proficiency includes good communication skills in both listening and speaking, and the ability to read and write documents in English.

Additionally, I am proficient in using project management tools such as Git, IDEs such as Visual Studio Code, and various tools such as Photoshop or Figma.

# **EDUCATION**

09/2017 - 4/2023

**FPT UNIVERSITY - HOA LAC** | Software Engineering Major Bachelor's degree certificates. GPA: 6,94

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

04/2023 - 09/2024

## WORKING AT FPT FIS (1+ YEAR) | Fresher / Employee

- I gained valuable experience collaborating and contributing effectively as part of a team, working on both front-end and back-end tasks.
- I honed my skill in React.js development and experienced in utilizing various other front-end tools, backed by practical work experience in a professional setting.

04/2022 - 07/2022

#### 3 MONTHS OF FRESHER AT CMC GLOBAL | Fresher

- During this job, I became familiar with corporate procedures and completed online courses to enhance my skills.
- Additionally, I gained valuable insight into teamwork and developed the ability to effectively contribute as a member of a team. I also involved with a project to enhance my ReactJS / NextJS skill.

01/2020 - 07/2022

#### 3 MONTHS OF INTERNSHIP AT FSOFT | Intern

- I had the opportunity to immerse myself in various office tasks and environments, allowing me to gain valuable work experience, learn about work ethics and responsibilities.
- I also had the chance to work with tools like Git and utilize popular Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) such as NetBeans, VSCode, and PyCharm, which provided me with valuable hands-on experience.

#### **PROJECTS**

THESE ARE MY PERSONAL PROJECTS, PROJECTS THAT I HAVE PARTAKEN IN DURING MY WORKEXPERIENCE AND OTHER PROJECTS DURING MY UNIVERSITY EDUCATION:

(proficient), N5 Japanese

- Developed a user management web front using ReactJS for Dat Xanh Group: http://uat-admin.datxanh.com.vn/
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://duyhung2h.web.app/, written in ReactJs.
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://aislingvt.vercel.app/, written in ReactJs
- + NextJS + Vercel.
- Comic reading website: A Frontend project for reading different comics
- House rental website: A simple Frontend project for landlords to manage financial details.
- Nhà Hàng Ba Miền website: A Fullstack website platform for customers and managers, specialising in online food delivery
- Black League Shop website: A Fullstack website shoe shop platform for customers
- Project André: A Python project for my upcoming modded game project

# **GENERAL SKILLS & QUALITIES**

I'm Able to work with Different object-oriented programming languages such as Python, Java, Typescript,...

My Language skill: C1 English (proficient), N5 Japanese

I'm Familiar with project management models such as SCRUM, AGILE, Waterfall,...

I'm Able to work both independently or in a team environment.

I'm capable of Using Project management tools like Github, Gitlab or Git, and willing to learn different tools.

I have Proficient English skills, knowledgeable in using different writing or translating tools

Although A bit introverted, when it comes to work ethics, I'm meticulous and observant about any assigned task, and persistent in getting works done.

I have skills in video editing using Wondershare Filmora, and have some photoshop skills, and Audio editing skills using Audacity.

## **MORE INFO**

All of my different day-to-day hobbies!

- Playing and modifying video games
- Reading, writing in English
- History, world's cultures and geography
- Listening to podcasts and music
- Painting and arts